[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：我认为它会非常有用
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Thought it'd be useful to just very quickly
循环回去讨论一下这个关于thunk到底是什么的概念。
circle back to kind of talk about this notion of what a thunk really is.
实际上并不是所有这些，也不是真的那么特别，只是
And actually it's not all of that, it's not really all that special, it's just
也许是我们不太熟悉的回调模式的用法。
maybe a usage of the callback pattern that we aren't terribly familiar with.
我们中的大多数人可能至少对闭合有一些短暂的熟悉。
Most of us probably at least have some passing familiarity with closure.
这就是func的真正意义所在，它使用闭包来维护状态，
And that's really what the func is all about is using closure to maintain state,
为什么这很重要？
now why is that so important?
那么之前聊天上的一些问题是关于我们的想法吗？
So some questions on the chat before about what our thunks?
他们是在解决回叫地狱之类的事情吗？
Are they solving callback hell or things like that?
嗯，他们仍然是回调，所以
Well they're still callbacks so
他们并没有从根本上改变这个游戏。
they're not fundamentally changing that particular game.
回调并不是真的我的意思是thunks并没有真正添加任何东西
Callbacks aren't really I mean thunks are not really adding anything
在更好的可信度方面。
to the equation in terms of better trustability.
或者甚至我的意思是他们更合理一点，我想这个代码
Or even I mean they're a little bit more reasonable I suppose this code
显然比我们之前的常规回调更合理一些。
is clearly a bit more reasonable than what we had before with just regular callbacks.
但本质上它并不是更线性或顺序性，或同步性。
But it's not fundamentally more linear or sequential, or synchronous in nature.
所以在这方面真的没有太多的移动球。
So really hasn't moved the ball much on that respect.
所以，谢谢真的不是特别关于解决回拨地狱的。
So thanks really aren't specifically about solving callback hell.
但他们确实解决了一个非常重要的问题
But they do solve a really important problem that sets us up for
我们将在这个研讨会上讨论的其他内容。
the rest of the stuff that we're going to discuss in this workshop.
这就是为什么，我选择花时间去推动他们，
And that's why, I chose to spend time pushing on them,
这不仅仅是一件琐碎的事情，他们真的很重要
it's not just a trivia sort of thing that they really are an important
概念基础，我们在此基础上构建其余的东西。
conceptual foundation upon which we build the rest of stuff.
那么主要的事情就是主要的外卖，为什么thunk是这样的呢？
So the major thing the major takeaway, why is the thunk so
对我很重要为什么我要关心。
important to me why should I care.
为什么它应该是我武器库的一部分
And why should it be something that's part of my arsenal of
我用来解决异步编程问题的武器？
weapons that I used to take down asynchronous programming issues?
这样做的原因是，通过使用in中的闭包
Well the reason for that is, that by using the closure in the in
thunk模式通过使用闭包来维护某物的状态。
the thunk pattern by using the closure to maintain the state of something.
我们消除了时间作为国家的一个复杂因素。
We eliminate time as a complecting factor of state.
时间是程序中最复杂的状态因素。
Time is the most complex factor of state in your program.
理解事情发生的顺序和
Understanding the order in which things happen and
随着时间的推移，事情发生变化的方式是应用程序中最复杂的部分。
the way things change over time is the most complex part of your application.
这是我们最难思考的部分，这是不可能的吗？
It's the hardest part for us to reason about, is it impossible?
显然不是，但它确实让事情变得更难了。
Clearly not but it does make it harder.
所以如果我们可以使用这个工具，这个保持状态的概念
So if we can use this tool, this notion of preserving state
在这个值包装容器中，我们称之为thunk。
inside of this value wrapper container that we call a thunk.
然后我们可以将这些值组合在一起，并且
We then are able to compose these values together, and
不用担心顺序，时间就不成问题了。
not worry about the ordering, time becomes a non-issue.
正如您在这里看到的代码，我对thunk one thunk two和thunk one thunk two进行排序
As you can see here with this code, I am sequencing the thunk one thunk two and
把三个放在一起。
thunk three together.
我们已经了解了之前的解决方案，
And we know already having looked at the previous solution,
希望这在你们的脑海中足够新鲜。
hopefully that's fresh enough in your minds.
查看了此解决方案后，我们看到
Having looked at this solution we see that there is
基本上是一个比赛条件，如果你愿意的话。
basically a race condition if you will.
在它有之前我们是否要求它的反应，
Between whether we ask for the thunks response before it has it,
或者回答是否在询问之前返回。
or whether the response comes back before it's been asked.
那里有一个基本的种族条件，这是一个时间问题。
There's a fundamental race condition there, that's a time issue.
这是一个复杂的问题，我们必须在前一个练习中自行处理
That's a complexity issue that we had to manage ourselves in the previous exercise
通过编写所有的循环垃圾和
by writing all that for loop crap and
在全局变量中填充内容。
stuffing things inside of a global variable.
这种复杂性是我们必须自己解决的问题
That complexity is something that we had to solve ourselves
这个模式为我们解决了这个问题。
this pattern solves that for us.
它采用了一个值并消除了时间作为关注点，这并不意味着
It takes a value and eliminates the time as the concern, it doesn't mean
它消除了所有的顾虑，但我们最复杂的顾虑被消除了。
it eliminates all concerns but the most complex of our concerns is eliminated.
它甚至没有真正被消除，它只是简单地被抽象掉了。
It's not even really eliminated, it's just simply abstracted away.
所以这不是我们在代码中需要关心的事情
So it's not something we have to be concerned about in the parts of our code
我们消费这些问题，消费这些价值。
where we're consuming these issues, consuming these values.
所以如果你愿意，我们写一次管道，
So we write the plumbing once if you will,
就像我刚才给你们展示的那样，创造Thunk的机制。
the mechanism by which a thunk is created as I showed you just there.
然后在我们使用它的地方，是线41到50代表
And then where we use it, it's the lines 41 through 50 that represent
我们反复编写的大部分代码。
the bulk of our code that we write over and over and over again.
我们编写代码来推断正在发生的异步操作和
We write code to reason about asynchronous actions that are occurring and
这是一种明显更合理的代码。
this is the kind of code that is significantly more reasonable.
因为在这个问题上我们不必担心时间。
Than it was before because we don't have to worry about time in this issue.
这才是最重要的，我反复强调这一点，因为我认为
That's what is so important and I'm harping on this so much because I think
我们将要谈论的下一个话题，我们将跳跃到承诺中。
the next topic that we're about to talk about we're about to jump into promises.
我认为人们在很大程度上忽略了为什么承诺是如此的重要
And I think the point has largely been missed about why promises are so
革命性的。
revolutionary.
我认为大多数人都把重点放在承诺作为API和
I think most people have focused on promises as an API and
跟你说实话？
to be honest with you?
承诺的API是我最不感兴趣的部分。
The API for promises is the least interesting part to me.
对我来说更有趣的是承诺
It's far more interesting to me that promises
是我们内置的这种模式的资格。
are a qualification of this pattern built in for us.
所以我们甚至不需要像它所在的那样多地去思考它
So that we don't even really have to think about it as much it's even there for
我们自动。
us automatically.
这种管理国家模式的资格
A qualification of this pattern of managing state
以与时间无关的方式在包装器内部。
internal inside of a wrapper in a time independent way.
还有更多的承诺，但在和
There is more to promises than that, but the that in and
本身就是革命性的。
of itself is revolutionary.
它本身就给大众带来了我们本可以成为的东西
That in and of itself is bringing to the masses something which we could have been
一直在做。
doing all along.
但对于
But for
不管是什么原因，这不是我们花时间思考的事情。
whatever reason this wasn't something that we spent time thinking about.
我写了很多非常糟糕的异步代码，我希望我可以去
I've written an awful lot of really bad asynchronous code and I wish I could go
回来，并修复所有的东西，一直使用的模式，如歌曲。
back and fix all of that stuff to have been using a pattern like songs.
因为这会比我以前拥有的好很多，但是
Because this would have been a lot better than what I had before but
故事还没结束。
it's not the end of the story.
在这个工作坊里有更多的事情要做，还有更多的事情要做。
There's more to go, much more to go in this workshop.
因此，以此作为我们的基础是提醒我们所处的位置和
So with that as our foundation is a reminder of where we're at and
为什么雷鸣如此重要。
why thunks are so important.
让我们一头扎进去，谈谈承诺。
Let's dive in and talk about promises.